and and I think looks pretty good this
is a pretty nice community and it's
pretty beautiful up here you enjoy
living up here guys it's pretty
fantastic you know on the news what they
would make you believe that the war is
gonna end in the next hour if you want
world peace turn the TV off go take a
walk
you know that's what you have to do
right because there's great things going
on out there the network's make a lot of
money from fear all of them you know I
think fear should be a major in college
because it makes a lot are you free law
pre-med I'm pretty fear I'm gonna go to
fear school after this I'm gonna make a
lot of money because they say the
world's gotten so violent it's got the
world it never got violent there is no
God the world is in violence since the
beginning Cain killed Abel right Cain
killed Abel the third person on the
planet killed the fourth person on
planet we weren't even able to make it
to three people
before somebody wasn't murder at one
time a third of the people on the planet
were murderers right a third of the
people in the hood aren't murderers a
third of the people who own guns aren't
murderers a third of the people in jail
aren't even murderers San Quentin Folsom
Prison and Alcatraz are safer than the
book of Genesis you thought Compton and
Baghdad were tough tried downtown Eden
after the Sun Goes Down right there was
murder and violence at person three one
couple had two boys who had the world to
themselves and one of them was claiming
this town ain't big enough for the two
of us Cain killed 25 percent of the
world's population
that's more than Stalin Hitler Idi Amin
Pol Pot King Herod Genghis Khan the
English manifest destiny typhoid cancer
aids cooties all combined Cain killed a
third of the people he knew Athena three
people he killed one of them if you knew
Cain you had a 66 and 2/3 percent chance
of survival there's no such thing as the
good old days there was no perfect time
to be alive there was like one good day
it was half a day Adam and Eve were
naked
alone in an oasis lunchtime came people
got hungry apples were eating boom
Detroit
you